Guide to the Yale Glee Club Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Glee Club records
1854-2010
RU 342
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
149.5
(136 boxes)
The records consist of programs, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks, sheet music, posters, and press clippings documenting the activities of the Yale Glee Club. Also included is a notebook of signatures of Yale Glee Club associates who attended the 125th reunion in 1986.
Yale Glee Club
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 40 (YRG 40), Records of Yale clubs, societies, and organizations.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Yale Glee Club, 1990-2008.
Conditions Governing Access
While this collection as a whole is available for research, parts of it may be restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Biographical / Historical
Formal singing at Yale was given impetus when Gustave Stoeckel was authorized to teach that subject in 1855. The Yale Glee Club was founded in 1860 and, by the late 1860s, class glee clubs (usually about a dozen men) were common.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of programs, photographs, scrapbooks, songbooks, sheet music, posters, and press clippings documenting the activities of the Yale Glee Club. Also included is a notebook of signatures of Yale Glee Club associates who attended the 125th reunion in 1986.
College students -- Societies, etc.; Students' songs; Vocal groups; Yale University -- Songs and music; Yale University -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Students; Yale Glee Club
- Photograph of the Yale Glee and Banjo Club, Circa 1895; Accession 19ND-A-472; 0.02; (1 envelope) (Box 1)
- Records, 1871-1943; Accession 19ND-A-481
  - Songbook, 1871 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Records, 1879-1884 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Notebook, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Manager's records, 1890-1895 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - General ledger; report, 1903-1905 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cash book for concerts, 1903-1905 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, correspondence, tickets and receipts, 1879-1915 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Wartime preservation, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Autograph book for 125th reunion, 1986; Accession 1990-A-119
  - Autograph book for 125th reunion, 1986 (Box 1)
- Press releases, 1997; Accession 1998-A-045
  - Press releases, 1997 (Box 1)
- Sheet music of "Columbia: Words and Music by Timothy Dwight (1752-1817) Arr. M.B." with Glee Club stamp, undated; Accession 2006-A-185
  - Sheet music of "Columbia: Words and Music by Timothy Dwight (1752-1817) Arr. M.B." with Glee Club stamp, undated (Box 1)
- 84th annual commencement concert poster, circa 1952; Accession 2006-A-259
  - 84th annual commencement concert poster, circa 1952 (Box 1)
- Records, 1854-2007; Accession 2007-A-105
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged by type of material.
  - Administrative records, 1901-2006
    - Seasons 41, 51, 1901-1902, 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Seasons 91-93, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Seasons 100-102, 104, 1961, 1963, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Seasons 106, 108-111, 113, 1967-1971, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Seasons 126, 129, 132, 135, 1986, 1989-1990, 1993, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Seasons 140-141, 144-145, 2001-2002, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified seasons, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1950-2004
    - Seasons 90-94, 1950-1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Seasons 95, 97, 99, 101-104, 1955-1965 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Seasons 105-107, 109, 1966-1968, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Seasons 132, 135, 143, 1993, 1995, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - no date, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, 1854-2005
    - Season 69, 1929-1930 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Season 70, 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Season 73, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Season 81: Pan-American tour, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Season 88
      - YGC, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - European tour, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 18 - 20)
    - Season 92, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Season 93, 1953-1954 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Season 94
      - European tour, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - 100 Years of Undergraduate Music, 1955, 1955 January 21 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Season 95, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Season 97
      - YGC, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - European tour, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Season 98: Anniversary reunion, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Season 98/99: YGC, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Season 100
      - YGC, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Latin American tour, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - South American tour, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Season 100/101: Lima [Peru], 1961 July 4 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Season 102: European tour, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Season 104: Around the World tour, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Season 105, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Season 106, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Season 107, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Season 109: European tour, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Season 109-110: Paris, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Season 111, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Season 113, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Season 114, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Season 116, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Season 117, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Season 127
      - Mory's Cup presentation, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Unidentified photographs, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 47 - 52)
      - Unidentified photographs [includes negatives], 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 53 - 58)
    - Season 128-129: Robert Shaw, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Season 133
      - Retreat [includes negatives], 1993 [Sep] (Box 5, Folder 60 - 61)
      - Yale-Harvard and Yale Club of NYC [includes negatives], 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 62)
      - Inauguration [includes negatives], 1993 [Nov] (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - Singing dinner [includes negatives], 1994 [Apr] (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Mahler concert [includes negatives], 1994 Spring (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - 1993 football game and Halloween Show [includes negatives] (Box 5, Folder 66 - 67)
      - Princeton [includes negatives], 1993 (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - YGC, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - Miscellaneous photographs [includes negatives], 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 70 - 71)
      - Winter tour, Southeast, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 72 - 75)
      - Winter tour, Southeast negatives, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Season 134: Photos from concert [includes negatives], circa 1995 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Season 135: Summer tour (Asia), 1996 (Box 6, Folder 78 - 84)
    - Season 138: 100thfootball Concert Singing Dinner, 1999 November (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Season 139, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Season 140
      - Officer's Hike first rehearsal [includes negatives], 2000 September (Box 7, Folder 87)
      - Retreat [includes negatives], 2000 September (Box 7, Folder 88)
      - Parents' Day, Polish Choir [includes negatives], 2000 October (Box 7, Folder 89)
      - Parents' Day, Tercentennial, Silliman Screw [includes negatives], 2000 October (Box 7, Folder 90)
      - YGC-band football game, Princeton party and Harvard rehearsal [includes negatives], 2000 November (Box 7, Folder 91 - 92)
      - Princeton Concert [includes negatives], 2000 November (Box 7, Folder 93 - 94)
      - Harvard Concert [includes negatives], 2000 November (Box 7, Folder 95 - 96)
      - Rivak (?) in NY, Christmas concert [includes negatives], 2000 December (Box 7, Folder 97)
      - Colorado tour, 147-171 [index cards only], 2001 January (Box 7, Folder 98)
      - UGC rehearsal in NH, end of CO tour [negatives only], 2001 January (Box 7, Folder 99)
      - Verdi at Carnegie, Tercentennial Light and Royal Blue [includes negatives], 2001 April (Box 7, Folder 100)
      - Verdi rehearsal warm up, concert New Haven [includes negatives], 2001 April (Box 7, Folder 101)
      - Verdi rehearsal, reunion [ includes negatives], 2001 April (Box 7, Folder 102)
      - Reunion [includes negatives], 2001 April (Box 7, Folder 103)
      - Officer's Mory's Night, YGC Mory's Night [includes negatives], 2001 May (Box 7, Folder 104)
      - UGC Concert and Afterglow, Verdi retreat, doubles party [includes negatives], 2000 December-2001 March (Box 7, Folder 105)
      - 2000-2001 [includes negatives] (Box 7, Folder 106)
      - Chamber Singers Brahms -pictures by David [includes negatives], 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 107 - 108)
    - Season 141
      - Africa tour photos, 2002 Summer (Box 8, Folder 109 - 121)
      - Africa tour photos, 2002 Summer (Box 9, Folder 122 - 132)
      - Africa tour index photographs [Kodak Advantix], 2002 Summer (Box 9, Folder 133)
      - Africa tour negatives, 2002 Summer (Box 9, Folder 134 - 136)
    - Seasons 140-144, 2000-2005 (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Season 142, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Season 145: Reunion concert, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Unidentified Seasons
      - Candid, travel, performance
        - circa 1930s (Box 10, Folder 140)
        - circa 1940s (Box 10, Folder 141)
        - circa 1950s (Box 10, Folder 142 - 148)
        - circa 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 149)
      - Apollo Glee Club, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 150)
      - Candid, travel, performance, circa 1960s (Box 11, Folder 151 - 152)
      - Around the world tour, circa 1960s (Box 11, Folder 153)
      - Candid, travel, performance
        - circa 1962-1965 (Box 11, Folder 154 - 158)
        - circa 1960s-1970s (Box 11, Folder 159)
        - circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 160)
      - Reunion, circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 161)
      - Candid, travel, performance
        - circa 1980s (Box 11, Folder 162)
        - circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 163)
    - Subjects
      - Alumni, circa 1998-2003 (Box 12, Folder 164 - 165)
      - Candid, social, travel, circa 1998-2003 (Box 12, Folder 166 - 172)
      - David Connell, circa 1998-2003 (Box 13, Folder 173)
      - Group photos, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 13, Folder 174)
      - Heath family, circa 1998-2003 (Box 13, Folder 175)
      - Individuals, undated (Box 13, Folder 176)
      - Managers, 1930-1961 (Box 13, Folder 177 - 181)
      - Performances, circa 1998-2003 (Box 14, Folder 182 - 189)
      - Pruett family, circa 1998-2003 (Box 14, Folder 190)
      - Peter Sipple, circa 1998-2003 (Box 14, Folder 191)
      - Yale Singers, circa 1854 (Box 14, Folder 192)
  - Posters
    - Seasons 91-93, 1951-1954 (Box 22, Folder 193)
    - Seasons 92-94, 1952-1955 (Box 18)
    - Seasons 95-97, 1955-1958 (Box 19)
    - Seasons 97-109, 1958-1970 (Box 21)
    - Seasons 100-101, 103, 105-107, 1961-1968 (Box 22, Folder 194)
    - [International Tours] Seasons 100, 102, 119, 1961-1980 (Box 37)
    - Seasons 110-114, 1970-1975 (Box 25)
    - Seasons 111, 117?, undated, 1971-1977 (Box 42)
    - Seasons 112, 114, 116, 120, 123, 1972-1984 (Box 27)
    - Seasons 115-119, 1975-1980 (Box 28)
    - Seasons 120-122, 1980-1983 (Box 29)
    - Seasons 123-124, 1983-1985 (Box 30)
    - Seasons 125-126, 1985-1987 (Box 31)
    - Seasons 127-129, 1987-1990 (Box 32)
    - Season 130, 1990-1991 (Box 33)
    - Seasons 131-132, 1991-1993 (Box 34)
    - Seasons 133-136, 1993-1997 (Box 35)
    - Seasons 136-139, 1996-1999 (Box 22, Folder 195)
    - Season 137, 1997-1998 (Box 38)
    - Season 138, 1998-1999 (Box 39)
    - Season 139, 1999-2000 (Box 41)
    - Season 140, 2000-2001 (Box 40)
    - Seasons 140, 142-146, 2000-2006 (Box 22, Folder 196)
    - Season 141, 2001-2002 (Box 43)
    - Seasons 142-143, 2002-2004 (Box 44)
    - Season 144, 2004-2005 (Box 45)
    - Season 145, 2005-2006 (Box 15)
    - Season 146, 2006-2007 (Box 26)
    - No date (Box 16)
    - No date, undated (Box 22, Folder 197)
  - Press
    - Seasons 10, 52-55, 1871, 1912-1916 (Box 23)
    - Season 80, 1940-1941 (Box 23)
    - Seasons 87, 93, 1948, 1954 (Box 23)
    - Seasons 95, 97, 99, 1956-1960 (Box 22)
    - Seasons 100, 102-103, 1960-1964 (Box 22)
    - Season 104, 1964-1966 (Box 22)
    - Seasons 105-107, 1965-1968 (Box 22)
    - Seasons 112, 114, 116, 120, 123, 1972-1984 (Box 22)
    - Seasons 144-145, 2004-2006 (Box 22)
    - No date (Box 22)
  - Programs
    - Seasons 10, 25, 30, 1870, 1885-1886, 1890 (Box 24, Folder 195)
    - Season 51, 1911-1912 (Box 24, Folder 196)
    - Seasons 52, 61, 67, 72-73, 1912-1934 (Box 24, Folder 197)
    - Seasons 80, 88-89, 1941, 1948-1950 (Box 24, Folder 198)
    - Seasons 90-91, 1950-1952 (Box 24, Folder 199)
    - Season 92, 1952-1953 (Box 24, Folder 200-201)
    - Seasons 93-94, 1953-1955 (Box 24, Folder 202)
    - Season 95, 1955-1956 (Box 27)
    - Seasons 96, 1956-1957 (Box 27)
    - Seasons 97, 99, 1957-1958, 1960 (Box 27)
    - Seasons 100, 102-103, 1960-1964 (Box 27)
    - Season 104, 1964-1965 (Box 27)
    - Seasons 105-106, 1965-1967 (Box 36)
    - Season 107, 1967-1968 (Box 36)
    - Seasons 108-109, 1968-1970 (Box 36)
    - Seasons 110-112, 114, 1970-1975 (Box 36)
    - Seasons 115-119, 1975-1980 (Box 36)
    - Seasons 120-124, 1980-1985 (Box 17)
    - Seasons 125-129, 1985-1990 (Box 17)
    - Seasons 130-132, 1990-1993 (Box 17)
    - Seasons 133-134, 1993-1995 (Box 17)
    - Seasons 135-137, 1995-1998 (Box 17)
    - Seasons 138-139, 1998-2000 (Box 17)
    - Season 140, 2000-2001 (Box 20)
    - Season 141, 2001-2002 (Box 20)
    - Seasons 142-143, 2002-2004 (Box 20)
    - Season 144, 2004-2005 (Box 20)
    - Season 145, 2005-2006 (Box 20)
- Scrapbooks, 1854-1999; Accession 2008-A-119
  - 1921-1928 (Box 1)
  - TOUR, 1928, 1932 (Box 2)
  - 1928-1933 (Box 3)
  - 1933-1935 (Box 4)
  - TOUR, 1935 (Box 5)
  - 1935-1940 (Box 6)
  - TOUR, 1936, 1939 (Box 7)
  - 1940-1946 (Box 8)
  - TOUR, 1941 (Box 9)
  - 1946-1949 (Box 10)
  - 1949 (Box 11)
  - 1949-1950 (Box 12)
  - 1951 (Box 13)
  - 1951-1952 (Box 14)
  - 1952-1953 (Box 15)
  - 1953-1954 (Box 16)
  - TOUR, 1954 (Box 17)
  - 1954-1955 (Box 18)
  - 1955-1956 (Box 19)
  - TOUR, 1956 (Box 20)
  - 1956-1957 (Box 21)
  - 1957-1958 (Box 22)
  - TOUR, 1958 (Box 23)
  - 1958-1959 (Box 24)
  - 1959-1960 (Box 25)
  - 1960-1961 (Box 26)
  - TOUR, 1961 (Box 27)
  - 1961-1962 (Box 28)
  - 1962-1963 (Box 29)
  - TOUR, 1963 (Box 30)
  - 1963-1964 (Box 31)
  - 1964-1965 (Box 32)
  - TOUR, 1965 (Box 33)
  - TOUR, 1965 (Box 34)
  - 1965-1966 (Box 35)
  - 1966-1967 (Box 36)
  - 1970-1971 (Box 37)
  - 1971-1972 (Box 38)
  - TOUR, 1973 (Box 39)
  - 1973-1974 (Box 40)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 41)
  - TOUR, 1977 (Box 42)
  - 1977-1978 (Box 43)
  - 1978-1979 (Box 44)
  - 1979-1980 (Box 45)
  - TOUR, 1980 (Box 46)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 47)
  - TOUR, 1983-1984 (Box 48)
  - 1984-1985 (Box 49)
  - 1986-1987 (Box 50)
  - TOUR, 1987 (Box 51)
  - 1989-1990 (Box 52)
  - TOUR, 1990 (Box 53)
  - 1990-1991 (Box 54)
  - 1992-1993 (Box 55)
  - TOUR, 1993 (Box 56)
  - 1994-1995 (Box 57)
  - 1995-1996 (Box 58)
  - TOUR, 1996 (Box 59)
  - 1998-1999 (Box 60)
- Records, 1877-2010; Accession 2008-A-142
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 15-17 are restricted until January 1, 2040 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
  Accession 2008-A-142 consists of Glee Club records, 1877-2008, including photographs, administrative files, press files, concert programs, fliers, and posters.
  - Photographs, 1894-2006
    - Season 34, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      General
      Folder empty when received.
    - Season 60, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Season 67: Europe tour, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Includes photocopy of group shot with no original.
    - Season 71: Budapest, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Photocopies with no originals.
    - Unidentified season, 1930s (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Season 80: South America tour, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Season 84, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Season 88, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified seasons, 1940s (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Season 88: Europe tour, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 6-9)
      Includes photographs and negatives from Murray Dodge '50.
    - Unidentified season, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
      Photographs and negatives from Murray Dodge '50.
    - Season 90
      - Yale Glee Club (YGC), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Caribbean tour, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Season 93: Europe tour, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Season 94: Smith-Apollo, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Season 95: Apollo Glee Club (AGC), 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Season 96: AGC, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Season 97
      - AGC, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - YGC, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Season 97: Europe tour, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Season 98
      - YGC, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - FGC, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Season 99
      - Freshman Glee Club (FGC), 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - AGC, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Season 100
      - Latin America tour, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - YGC, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - AGC, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - FGC, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Season 101
      - YGC, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - AGC, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - FGC, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Whiffenpoofs, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - "local boy" -- Christmas tour, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Season 102
      - FGC, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - YGC, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Europe tour, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Season 103: YGC, AGC, Yale Freshman Chorus (YFC), 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Season 104
      - YGC, YFC, Whiffenpoofs, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Round the World tour, 1965 Summer (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Season 105: YGC, YFC, unnamed, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Season 106: Corning Hospital, 1966 December (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Season 107
      - YGC, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Christmas tour, 1967 December (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Season 108: YGC, YFC, AGC, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Season 109
      - YGC (negative), 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Ed Sullivan, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Undated 1960s photos: Fenno Heath, AGC, FGC, YGC, "hometown boys", Charlotte Peters, unidentified, Circa 1960s (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Season 110: YGC, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Season 111
      - YGC, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Whiffenpoofs, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Press photos, 1971 Fall (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Season 112
      - YGC, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Commencement Concert party, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        Photographs by Maggie Rozas.
      - Fenno portraits, 1973 May (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Season 113: YGC, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Season 114
      - YGC, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Reprints of old Barty pictures for his 90th birthday, 1975 March (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Central America tour, 1975 Summer (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
    - Season 115, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Fenno and soloists, oversize, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Season 116: YGC, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Season 117
      - YGC rehearsal photos, 1977 October 10 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - YGC outdoor photos, 1978 Summer (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - U.S. ambassador's house, Argentina, 1978 July (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Season 118: Argentine choral visit, 1979 February (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Undated 1970s photos: singing dinners, Fenno Heath with others, unidentified, Circa 1970s (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Includes singing dinner at Rupert's Brewery featuring Prescott Bush, with Barty conducting. Photographs by Agnew Fisher, Greenwich, CT.
    - Season 119
      - YGC, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - "A Salute to Yale Singing", 1980 April (Box 3, Folder 1)
        Concert featurning Sir George Solti, Leontyne Price, and the Chicago Symphony Orchestra for the benefit of the Marshall Bartholomew Professorship of Choral Music.
    - Season 121
      - YGC, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Duke's Men, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Season 122: YGC, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Season 123: YGC, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Season 124, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Season 125: 125th Anniversary concert, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Consists of photographs of concert and surrounding events, probably sent in by alumni in response to letter from Fenno Heath.
      - Group portrait, oversize, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Season 126: rehearsal, official photos, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Season 127: official black and white photos, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Season 128: YGC, official black and white, color, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Season 129: official black and white, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Undated 1980s photographs
      - Richard Marlow, organist, publicity photo, Circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - King's Singers, Circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Fenno Heath, Circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Teddy bear, Circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Washington, D.C., Circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Philadelphia, Circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - In transit, Circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Undated mini prints, 1982-1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Season 130
      - YGC, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Reunion, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Season 131: YGC, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Season 132
      - Official black & white photographs, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Italy tour, 1993 June (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Season 133: black & white performance, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Season 135
      - Reunion, 1996 February 24 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - National Arts Council, 1996 Spring (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Asia tour, 1996 Summer (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Season 135: California, 1997 January (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Season 137: YGC, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Season 138
      - Freshman Chorus, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Europe tour, 1999 Summer
        - Photographs (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
        - Negatives (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Undated 1990s photographs
      - Commencement, senior night (Includes negatives.), Circa 1990s (Box 4A, Folder 1)
      - Beach negatives, Circa 1990s (Box 4A, Folder 1)
    - Season 139
      - YGC, 1999-2000 (Box 4A, Folder 2)
      - Bulldog Days recruitment, Mory's, Commencement, 2000 Spring (Box 4A, Folder 2)
      - Commencement and senior night, 2000 Spring (Box 4A, Folder 2)
      - Spring tour, 2000 Spring (Box 4A, Folder 2)
    - Season 140: Yale Club of New York City, 2000 December (Box 4A, Folder 3)
    - Season 141
      - YGC, 2001-2002 (Box 4A, Folder 3)
      - Africa tour, 2002 Summer (Box 4A, Folder 3)
    - Season 142: YGC, 2002-2003 (Box 4A, Folder 3)
    - Season 143: YGC, 2004 (Box 4A, Folder 3)
    - Season 144: YGC, 2004-2005 (Box 4A, Folder 3)
    - Season 145
      - Fall Retreat, 2005 Fall (Box 4A, Folder 4)
      - East Coast tour, 2006 (Box 4A, Folder 4)
      - Karaoke, 2005-2006 (Box 4A, Folder 4)
    - Undated photographs, no decade indicated
      - Whiffenpoofs at Mory's, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 5)
      - Winter trip including Rochester, NY, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 5)
      - Detroit, MI, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 5)
      - Apollo or Freshman Glee Club, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 5)
      - Major concert with orchestra, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 5)
      - Unidentified portrait, probably a "hometown boy" photo from a tour, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified negatives, Undated (Box 4A, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1880-2010
    Also includes some itineraries, articles, correspondence, tickets, and advertisements, as well as programs and other material relating to other organizations.
    - Season 16, 1887 June 27 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Seasons 24-25, 1885-1886, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence from donor, Thomas Darling, Jr. '25, 1992-1993.
    - Season 43, 1903 August 26 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Seasons 50-51, 1911 December 21 (Box 5, Folder 3)